yorkvilleu.ca 2012-12-29

# Privacy Statement | Yorkville University

## Privacy Statement

When you visit Yorkville University’s Web site, the server automatically collects a limited amount of information essential for the site’s operation and security. This information includes your IP address, the name of your Internet Service Provider, and information concerning your browser and operating system. Such information is used to perform statistical analysis of user trends and interests, and to help us make this site more useful to visitors. Yorkville University makes limited use of “cookies” which track your browser’s use of our site. Cookies are used for purposes such as ensuring that procedures (such as Library procedures) work properly.

Yorkville University’s Web site (www.yorkvilleu.ca) provides information about the University and its programs and services. It does not disclose any information obtained from this site to any other third party.

When you use Yorkville University’s Web site for program or services purposes, such as participating in online courses, requesting services, completing a questionnaire, or making payment, the personal information you provide for that program or service will be in compliance with Canada Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (2000) and will be used only for the purpose it was collected. The information will be disclosed only in accordance with the provisions of the Act (See Sections 4.3.1 through 4.3.7)

The personal information collected on this site - including any other information deemed part of a student’s record - will be used for the purpose of admission, registration, issuing income tax receipts, sending educational material and information, and for university research and planning. Certain personal information will also be disclosed to Statistics Canada, as required by the Statistics Act (Canada). This information will be protected by the New Brunswick Protection of Personal Information Act. If you have any questions about the collection and use of this information, contact our offices.[](mailto:jmclaughlin@yorkvilleu.ca)

Users can modify or delete the personal information collected on our websites by emailing [kmarques@yorkvilleu.ca](mailto:kmarques@yorkvilleu.ca).

Users can opt out of further communications from the school at any time by contacting [kmarques@yorkvilleu.ca](mailto:kmarques@yorkvilleu.ca) or selecting the unsubscribe link on emails received from the school. 

The Yorkville University Web site has links to outside Web pages. Please be aware that the University is not responsible for site content outside our Web site, or the privacy policies of outside Web sites. We encourage you to read the individual privacy statements on each Web site you visit.

This privacy statement is intended to reflect the sites maintained by Yorkville University and it is subject to change.
